

### CONTACT

Mobile: +380 50 4411801 E-mail: Zorger27@GMail.com Skype: anatoliy.zorin

#### Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/anatolii-zorin

Github

github.com/Zorger27

# ANATOLII ZORIN

## — Web Developer —

I've always enjoyed creating something new. Programming helps to realise this desire.

**Since 2016**, I have combined the administrative work as CEO with the work of Digital Marketer (Google Adwords, Google Analytics, Search Engine Marketing), Web Designer (Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma) and Frontend Developer (Javascript/HTML/CSS).

**In 2020**, I took up intensive study of Backend (Java, Scala, Kotlin).

**In 2021**, I restored and updated my knowledge of Frontend (Vue, Angular, React).

I'm easy learning. I have good analytical skills.

I'm comfortable working in a team or solo.

### **PROJECTS**

### MY Curriculum VITAE (Landing page)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Grid CSS, FlexBox CSS

### Calculator (WEB-application)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

### Sidebar Menu (WEB-application)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Boxicons CSS, JavaScript

### Website template for a blogger (SPA)

Technologies: Vue.JS, HTML5, CSS3, TypeScript

#### To-Do list (WEB-application)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, FlexBox CSS, JavaScript

### Typical JavaScript interview tasks (WEB-application)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, FlexBox CSS, JavaScript

### **Dropdown Menu (WEB-application)**

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3

### Memory game (WEB-application)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, FlexBox CSS, JavaScript

### **EDUCATION**

09.1994 - 01.1999

#### Kyiv national university of trade and economics (KNUTE)

Accounting and Related Services

04.2017 - 11.2017

#### PROG.kiev.ua

Web-Designer (UI/UX Designer)

Frontend Developer

11.2020 - present

#### ITVDN - IT Video Developers Network

Java Developer

HTML Coder

JavaScript Developer

Angular Developer

React Developer

Frontend Developer

PHP Developer

Python Developer

11.2021 - present

### EnglishDom - English language

Elementary, Pre-Intermediate, Intermediate, Upper-Intermediate

### **EXPERIENCE**

09.2000 - present

### LIS Ltd.

CEO

Full enterprise management.

01.2017 - present

### Yugov & D Ltd.

CEO

Full enterprise management.

### LANGUAGES

English - Upper-Intermediate Spanish - Upper-Intermediate

### HARD SKILLS

- √ Html5, CSS3, JavaScript
- √ Vue.JS, Angular
- √ Git, Github
- √ Figma, Photoshop

### SOFT SKILLS

- √ Management
- √ Strategic Thinking
- ✓ Critical Thinking
- √ Negotiation

#### 1. JAVA DEVELOPER (TP31617068D | 12.04.2021)

- 1) Java Starter (TP41734788 | 17.06.2021)
- 2) Java Essential (TP85302318 | 16.01.2021)
- 3) Java Advanced 2021 (TP73439317 | 11.08.2021)
- 4) SOLID principles in Java (TP00933660 | 14.12.2020)
- 5) Unit testing with JUnit (TP52431470 | 23.03.2021)
- 6) Java Database Connectivity (TP57486314 | 28.02.2021)
- 7) JDBC & Hibernate (TP00684634 | 04.03.2021)
- 8) Java EE Basic (TP12409765 | 16.03.2021)
- 9) Spring Framework (TP05064920 | 08.02.2021)
- 10) Spring MVC (TP41523672 | 14.02.2021)
- 11) Spring Data (TP19471428 | 27.03.2021)
- 12) Spring Security (TP52120949 | 29.03.2021)
- 13) Web Services Development (TP14941346 | 12.04.2021)
- 14) Jenkins (TP93023078 | 15.06.2021)
- 15) Thymeleaf Patterns Engine (TP16212701 | 17.04.2021)
- 16) Scala Starter (TP28012733 | 02.04.2021)
- 17) Scala Essential (TP41881134 | 07.04.2021)
- 18) Scala Advanced (TP70826526 | 05.05.2021)
- 19) Kotlin (TP51225757 | 25.04.2021)
- 20) Asynchronous programming (TP33405544 | 28.09.2021)
- 21) Design Patterns in Java (TP37097304 | 06.11.2021)

#### 2. PHP DEVELOPER (TP88892276D | 30.09.2022)

- 1) PHP 8.0 Starter (TP45675166 | 17.08.2022)
- 2) PHP 7.4 Essential (TP92998740 | 01.09.2022)
- 3) PHP Advanced (TP47801691 | 28.09.2022)
- 4) Laravel (TP85284868 | 10.09.2022)
- 5) Magento 2 (TP17795504 | 14.09.2022)
- 6) YII2 Essential (TP21584504 | 22.09.2022)
- 7) YII2 Advanced (TP21335122 | 26.09.2022)
- 8) Symfony Web Development (TP16870523 | 30.09.2022)

#### 3. Python Developer (TP45473683D| 16.11.2022)

- 1) Python 3.8.6 Starter (TP34890769 | 07.10.2022)
- 2) Python 3.8.6 Essential (TP37206931 | 18.10.2022)
- 3) Python Advanced (TP30334066 | 25.10.2022)
- 4) Flask (TP35918152 | 28.10.2022)
- 5) Django Starter (TP36453931 | 10.11.2022)
- 6) Django Essential (TP28729679 | 16.11.2022)

### 4. Ruby Developer

- 1) Ruby Essential (TP72010831 | 21.11.2022)
- 2) Ruby Advanced (TP80374246 | 22.11.2022)

### OTHER CERTIFICATES

- 1) Git basics (TP37589708 | 18.03.2021)
- 2) Linux administration basics (TP03316433 | 12.10.2021)
- 3) Golang (TP09903227 | 22.10.2021)

#### 1. HTML CODER (TP24303907D | 16.06.2021)

- 1) HTML5&CSS3 Starter 2022 (TP37225065 | 09.08.2022)
- 2) HTML5&CSS3 Essential (TP24244286 | 16.06.2021)
- 3) HTML5&CSS3 Advanced (TP92660322 | 04.06.2021)
- 4) Layout of pages using Grid (TP62170279 | 31.05.2021)
- 5) Bootstrap 4 (TP33638993 | 27.05.2021)
- 6) Practical Landing Course (TP73961983 | 09.06.2021)
- 7) WordPress Starter (TP68763365 | 10.07.2021)
- 8) WordPress Essential (TP85465557 | 13.07.2021)

### 2. JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER (TP84806711D | 01.07.2021)

- 1) JavaScript Starter (TP47415802 | 14.05.2021)
- 2) JavaScript Essential 2021 (TP26716836 | 22.07.2021)
- 3) JavaScript Patterns (TP95784000 | 25.06.2021)
- 4) ECMAScript 6 (TP61852573 | 28.06.2021)
- 5) JavaScript Extended (TP59539891 | 30.06.2021)

### 3. Angular Developer (TP31003654D | 02.08.2021)

- 1) TypeScript Fundamentals (TP81113114 | 21.03.2021)
- 2) Angular 2.0 Essential (TP75000423 | 29.07.2021)
- 3) Angular 11.0 Essential (TP23149294 | 16.08.2021)
- 4) Angular Advanced (TP01762348 | 02.08.2021)

### 4. REACT DEVELOPER (TP37723782D | 09.08.2021)

- 1) React Essential (TP20433727 | 05.08.2021)
- 2) React Advanced (TP74208807 | 09.08.2021)
- 3) React Native (TP06814422 | 19.08.2021)

### 5. FRONTEND DEVELOPER (TP77692345D | 12.08.2021)

- 1) Vue.js Starter (TP75556859 | 11.08.2021)
- 2) Vue.js Essential (TP51164572 | 17.08.2021)
- 3) Building site with Vue.js (TP29746655 | 23.08.2021)
- 4) jQuery 2021 (TP55404559 | 23.09.2021)
- 5) Web Components (TP75653206 | 30.07.2021)

#### 6. UX/UI DESIGNER

- 1) UX/UI Design Starter (TP08523730 | 18.05.2021)
- 2) UX/UI Design Essential (TP37142600 | 20.05.2021)
- 3) UX/UI Mobile App Design (TP57418431 | 23.05.2021)
- 4) Figma. Online store design (TP46637985 | 25.07.2021)

### 7. DATABASE DEVELOPER

- 1) Transact SQL (TP71375264 | 26.01.2021)
- 2) MySQL (TP99655661 | 23.02.2021)
- 3) PostgreSQL (TP84560502 | 20.04.2021)
- 4) MongoDB (TP56496721 | 21.04.2021)

#### 8. PROJECT MANAGEMENT

- 1) Introduction to PM (TP84744235 | 27.04.2021)
- 2) Scrum and PM Methodologies (TP14623786 | 15.02.2021)

### 9. English language

- 1) English for IT (Pre-Intermediate | 01.12.2021)
- 2) Business English (Pre-Intermediate | 15.12.2021)
- 3) Intermediate level of English (Intermediate | 09.01.2022)
- 4) English for advanced (Upper-Intermediate | 14.02.2022)